WAGNER SILVEIRA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

+551899191-6291

wagner.resta@outlook.com

SKILLS

C#.NET HTMI Laravel Codeigniter PHP Jquery VueJS React.JS CSS

EDUCATION

Analysis and systems Development Centro Universitário UNIFAEL

LANGUAGES

English Portuguese



PROFILE

FullStack Developer with more than 12 years of experience. I like to develop software and systems that make people's daily lives easier, making tasks easier and more fun. Main Skills: NET, PHP, LARAVEL, VUEJS, REACT, JS, REST. Also, worked with digital transformation making integrations between legacy system and devops. Main Tools: Github, Bitbucket, Gitlab, PhpUnit. Cloud Knowledge: Aws: Ecs2 Azure: CosmoDb Azure Databse Studio Google: Firebase Firestore Cloud functions Google **Drive Google Docs Integrations**

WORK EXPERIENCE

FullStack Developer

2021 - 2024

· Development of new functions for the company's system, maintenance of existing functionalities in PHP, Laravel and VueJS.

- Technologies:
 - o PHP
 - Laravel
 - VueJS
 - Mysql
 - PHPUnit
 - o Jenkins

FullStack Developer

GW 2016 - 2021

Responsible for designing, modifying and maintaining web applications.

- Technologies:
 - o PHP
 - Laravel
 - o Codeigniter
 - Jquery
 - Mvsal
 - PHPUnit
 - o C#
 - o Razor MVC 5
 - Entity Framework
 - o SQL Server

Delphi Developer

Acert Group

2014 - 2016

- Responsible for designing, modifying and maintaining desktop applications.
- · Technologies:
 - o Delphi 10
 - Firebird Database

Java Teacher

2021 - 2024

• I created and implemented lesson plans, materials, instruction for students from 16 to 17 years old for courses in JAVA (Desktop Application), Office Package, Algorithms and Programming Logic, Html, PHP. Correction and elaboration of evaluations.

